在今天的阅读中，我们将讨论测试，
In today's reading we'll talk about testing,
这是最广泛使用的制作技术
which is the most widely used practical technique for making
代码安全。
code safe from bugs.
读完这篇文章，你应该明白
After this reading, you should understand
测试的价值，了解过程
the value of testing, know the process
对于测试优先编程，您应该
of test first programming, you should
能够为方法设计测试套件
be able to design a test suite for a method
通过划分输入和输出空间
by partitioning its input and output space
选择好的测试用例
and choosing good test cases, you
应该能够通过测量测试套件的代码来判断它
should be able to judge a test suite by measuring its code
覆盖范围，了解和了解
coverage, and understand and know
何时使用黑盒和白盒测试，
when to use black box and white box testing,
单元测试和集成测试，
unit tests, and integration tests,
以及自动化回归测试。
and automated regression testing.
我们开始吧。
Let's get started.